Register of the Raymond Albert Wheeler papers, 1898-1977
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1918-1974 (Boxes 8-12)
  - Snavely, Charles A., 1960 (Box-folder 12: 36)
  - Snell, Paul M., undated (Box-folder 12: 37)
  - Snow, Edgar, 1944 (Box-folder 12: 38)
  - Solleveld, J., 1957 (Box-folder 12: 39)
  - Spainhour, Emily, 1972 (Box-folder 12: 40)
  - Spencer, Abbott K., 1968 (Box-folder 12: 41)
  - Sprunt, James Lawrence, 1969 (Box-folder 12: 42)
  - Stanhope, William W., 1972 (Box-folder 12: 43)
  - Stennis, John, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 12: 44)
  - Stetson, John B., 1965 (Box-folder 12: 45)
  - Stillwell, J. W., 1942-1948 (Box-folder 12: 46)
  - Stratton, James H., 1963-1966 (Box-folder 12: 47)
  - Susong, Edith O'Keefe, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 12: 48)
  - Talaat, Ahmed, 1966 (Box-folder 12: 49)
  - Talley, B. B., 1964 (Box-folder 12: 50)
    Includes a letter to A. D. Spottswood.
  - Tallman, Gordon, 1966 (Box-folder 12: 51)
  - Thomas, Dorothy, 1969 (Box-folder 12: 52)
  - Thompson, L. I., 1968 (Box-folder 12: 53)
  - Tipton, Royce J., 1964 (Box-folder 12: 54)
  - Tomasulo, Nicholas A., 1965 (Box-folder 12: 55)
  - Toor, Z. A., 1967 (Box-folder 12: 56)
  - Tull, Willis C., Jr., 1965 (Box-folder 12: 57)
  - Tun, Hia?, 1970 (Box-folder 12: 58)
  - Urbahn, Max, 1965 (Box-folder 12: 59)
  - Varkas, Cessa, 1954 (Box-folder 12: 60)
  - Van Gasse, Josephine, 1965 (Box-folder 12: 61)
  - Vaughan, David B., 1964 (Box-folder 12: 62)
  - Veterans of the Office of Secret Services (William J. Casey and William J. Donovan), 1964-1966 (Box-folder 12: 63)
  - Vickers, W. G. H., 1944 (Box-folder 12: 64)
  - Vogel, Herbert D., 1968 (Box-folder 12: 65)
  - Volpe, John, 1972 (Box-folder 12: 66)
  - Wavell, Archibald Percival Wavell, Earl of, 1943-1953 (Box-folder 12: 67)
  - Weart, D. L., 1965 (Box-folder 12: 68)
  - Webb, Del E., 1964 (Box-folder 12: 69)
  - Wedemeyer, A. C., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 12: 70)
    Includes Wedemeyer's remarks at the Office of Strategic Services dinner, 1966 March 21.
  - Wehle, Philip C., 1963 (Box-folder 12: 71)
  - Wheeler, Stephen W., 1966 (Box-folder 12: 72)
  - Whipple, William, Jr., 1960-1966 (Box-folder 12: 73)
  - White, David H., 1973 (Box-folder 12: 74)
  - Whitman, W. M., 1963 (Box-folder 12: 75)
  - Wilder, A. D., 1972 (Box-folder 12: 76)
  - Wilkinson, Peggy, 1958 (Box-folder 12: 77)
  - Witt, Jay, 1966 (Box-folder 12: 78)
  - Woods, George D., 1957-1965 (Box-folder 12: 79)
  - Young, Mason J., 1964-1968 (Box-folder 12: 80)
  - Yeager, L. E., 1963 (Box-folder 12: 81)
  - Younes, Mahmoud, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 12: 82)
  - Youngblood, J. M. K., 1960 (Box-folder 12: 83)
  - Zimmerman, George J., 1944 (Box-folder 12: 84)
- Speeches and Writings, 1903-1970 (Boxes 13-14)
  Articles, comments, congressional testimony, notes, outlines, remarks, statements, speeches, and related correspondence and telegrams, arranged chronologically.
  - "Notes on Service Overseas during Second World War," Vols. I-VI, typescript, undated (Box-folder 13: 1-6)
  - Obituary of Karl Slaughter Bradford, original draft by Raymond Wheeler and Karl Bradford, holograph and typescript, undated (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Opening statement, Indus Basin Conference, typescript, undated (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Remarks on the occasion of getting together with the troops in the India Burma Theater, typescript, undated (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Speech on Suez Canal clearance under the auspices of the United Nations, Twentieth Century Club, Young Women's Christian Association, typescript outline, undated (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - "Address of Welcome," The Opinion, holograph and printed copy, 1903 July (Box-folder 13: 11)
  - "The Infantry School," a history of the Fourth Engineers, typescript copies and holograph notes, undated (Box-folder 13: 12-13)
  - "Improving the Upper River," Chamber of Commerce News, printed copy, 1934 August (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Notes on travel, typescript, 1941 November (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Notes on travel, typescript, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - "Chindwin River Trip," typescript, 1945 April (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - "Rangoon Victory Parade Trip," typescript, 1945 June 13 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Talk to Staff Officers in India-Burma Theater, Delhi, India, typescript, 1945 June 23 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - "India Burma - Lifeline to China," United States at War, printed copy, 1945 November (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - "The U.S. Corps of Engineers," The Military Engineer, printed copy, 1946 May (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Welcome address, the Engineering School, Fort Belvoir, Virginia, printed copy, 1946 November 4 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - "The United States Army," American Miracle, printed copy, 1947 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Testimony, hearings before the Committee on Expenditures in the Executive Departments, United States Senate, printed copy, 1949 February 2-15 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Speech, the First Pan-American Engineering Congress, Rio de Janeiro, typescript, 1949 July 15-24 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - "Balance Sheets and Blue Prints," The Retired Officer, printed copy, 1951 June (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Outline for a talk, M. S. A., typescript, 1953 March 26 (Box-folder 14: 14)
  - Outline for a talk, American Society of Civil Engineers, typescript, 1953 May 6 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Untitled note, The Green Light, printed copy, 1956 February 29 (Box-folder 14: 16)
  - Outline for a talk, Society of American Military Engineers, typescript, 1956 April 17 (Box-folder 14: 17)
  - "Suez: The Beginning of Clearence Operations," International Bank Notes, printed copy, 1957 September (Box-folder 14: 18)
  - Speech on Suez operations, West Point Society, typescript outline, 1957 September 12 (Box-folder 14: 19)
  - Speech on Suez Canal clearance operations, Society of American Military Engineers, Hampton Roads, New York, typescript outline, 1957 September 30 (Box-folder 14: 20)
  - Notes on Peoria talk, Peoria, Illinois, typescript, 1957 October 5 (Box-folder 14: 21)
    Includes related correspondence and telegram.
  - Speech, American Institute of Consulting Engineers, New York, 1957 October 15 (Box-folder 14: 22)
    Includes a letter and typescript drafts.
  - "Clearing the Suez Canal," The Military Engineer, printed copy, 1958 January-February (Box-folder 14: 23)
  - Speech on Suez Canal clearance operations, University of Arkansas, typescript with some holograph notes, 1958 March 6 (Box-folder 14: 24)
  - Outline for a speech, Jango, typescript, 1958 May 20. (Box-folder 14: 25)
  - Speech, Society of American Military Engineers, Baltimore, Maryland, typescript outline with some holograph notes, 1958 May 28 (Box-folder 14: 26)
  - "Role of the Suez Canal," speech, Conference on Nationalism and Business Prospects in the Middle East, Hotel Statler, Washington D.C., 1958 September 29-30 (Box-folder 14: 27)
    Typescript outline with related correspondence, memoranda, and notes.
  - Comments on "The Military Engineer," typescript, 1958 December 22 (Box-folder 14: 28)
  - "The Suez Canal - Its Chronicle and Bibliography," discussions by Raymond Wheeler and others, Journal of the Waterways and Harbors Division, proceedings of the American Society of Civil Engineers, printed copy, 1959 March (Box-folder 14: 29)
  - Talk, Advanced Class, Ports and Harbors Instruction, Engineering School, Fort Belvoir, Virginia, typescript, 1959 April 21 (Box-folder 14: 30)
  - Speech on the occasion of the award of Hoover Medal, Society of Military Engineers, typescript, 1959 February 2 (Box-folder 14: 31)
  - Speech on the occasion of the Beaver award, typescript, 1960 January 13 (Box-folder 14: 32)
  - Talk on the World Bank - Projects and Logistics, National Security Industrial Association and National Institute of Packaging, Handling and Logistics Engineers, typescript, 1960 February 8 (Box-folder 14: 33)
  - Untitled draft of a talk, Peoria, Illinois, typescript, 1960 April 4 (Box-folder 14: 34)
  - "Per Angusta ad Augusta," speech, Peoria, Illinois, typescript, 1960 May 4 (Box-folder 14: 35)
  - Speech, Bradley University, Peoria, Illinois, typescript fragment, 1960 May 4 (Box-folder 14: 36)
    Includes related correspondence and brochure.
  - "International River Problems", speech, Peoria, Illinois, typescript, 1961 October 20 (Box-folder 14: 37)
    Includes brochure, clippings, related correspondence, and program.
  - Notes for a speech on Mekong River, AICE meeting, Lahore, Pakistan, typescript, 1962 December 11 (Box-folder 14: 38)
  - Speech to introduce Colonel Mahmoud Younes, Chairman and Managing Director, Suez Canal Authority, at a luncheon meeting, American-Arab Association, typescript, 1963 September 18 (Box-folder 14: 39)
  - Speech, Ohio Valley Improvement Association, Netherlands-Hilton Hotel, Cincinnati, Ohio, typescript outline, 1964 October 15 (Box-folder 14: 40)
  - "Earthmoving," G. Edwin Burks Lecture, Earthmoving Industry Conference, Society of Automotive Engineers, Peoria, Illinois, typescript outline, 1970 April 14-15 (Box-folder 14: 41)
    Includes related correspondence, holograph note, and pamphlet.
  - "50 Years of Our Society," The Military Engineer, printed copy, 1970 July-August (Box-folder 14: 42)
    This article is adapted from Wheeler's address at the Annual Meeting of the Society of American Military Engineers, Fort Myer, Virginia, 1970 May 15. Includes author's proof.
- United States Army File, 1903-1977 (Boxes 15-20)
  Bulletins, clippings, correspondence, diary, financial records, maps, memoranda, minutes of meetings, messages, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, printed matter, remarks, reports, service records, statements, telegrams, and writings by others related to the events of the years of Raymond Wheeler's service in, and later association with, the army, arranged chronologically and thereunder alphabetically by physical form. See also: Correspondence.
  - 1903-1941
    - General (Box-folder 15: 1)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Box-folder 15: 2)
      - 1915 (Box-folder 15: 3)
      - 1919 (Box-folder 15: 4)
      - 1926 (Box-folder 15: 5)
      - 1930 (Box-folder 15: 6)
      - 1933 (Box-folder 15: 7)
      - 1935 (Box-folder 15: 8)
      - 1938 (Box-folder 15: 9)
    - Diary, 1918 (Box-folder 15: 10)
    - Maps (Box-folder 15: 11)
    - Memoranda
      - 1910-1911 (Box-folder 15: 12-13)
      - 1916-1920 (Box-folder 15: 14-18)
      - 1929 (Box-folder 15: 19)
      - 1935-1936 (Box-folder 15: 20-21)
      - 1941 (Box-folder 15: 22)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 15: 23-24)
    - Newsletters, 1919-1933 (Box-folder 15: 25)
    - Notes (Box-folder 15: 26)
    - Pamphlets, 1903-1919 (Box-folder 15: 27)
    - Printed matter
      - Undated (Box-folder 15: 28)
      - 1914 (Box-folder 15: 29)
      - 1919 (Box-folder 15: 30-31)
    - Reports
      - Undated (Box-folder 15: 32)
      - 1918 (Box-folder 15: 33)
    - Service records (Box-folder 15: 34)
    - Telegrams
      - Undated (Box-folder 16: 1)
      - 1919 (Box-folder 16: 2)
      - 1926 (Box-folder 16: 3)
      - 1941 (Box-folder 16: 4)
    - Writings by others, undated (Box-folder 16: 5)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 16: 6)
  - 1942-1949
    - General (Box-folder 16: 7)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Box-folder 16: 8)
      - 1942-1943 (Box-folder 16: 9-10)
      - 1943-1947 (Box-folder 16: 11)
      - 1944-1945 (Box-folder 16: 12-13)
      - 1948 (Box-folder 16: 14)
    - Diary, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 16: 15)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Box-folder 16: 16)
      - 1942-1946 (Box-folder 16: 17-21)
      - 1948-1949 (Box-folder 16: 22-23)
    - Messages (Box-folder 16: 24)
    - News bulletins (Box-folder 16: 25)
    - Newsletters (Box-folder 16: 26)
    - Notes (Box-folder 16: 27)
    - Organizational chart (Box-folder 16: 28)
    - Pamphlets (Box-folder 16: 29)
    - Press releases (Box-folder 16: 30)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 16: 31-32)
    - Posters (Box-folder 16: 33)
    - Reports
      - 1943-1945 (Box-folder 17: 1)
      - 1943-1946 (Box-folder 17: 2)
      - 1945 (Box-folder 17: 3)
    - Retirement records
      - General (Box-folder 17: 4)
      - Correspondence, 1947, 1949 (Box-folder 17: 5-6)
      - Memoranda, 1947 (Box-folder 17: 7)
    - Service records (Box-folder 17: 8)
    - Telegrams
      - Undated (Box-folder 17: 9)
      - 1942 (Box-folder 17: 10)
      - 1945 (Box-folder 17: 11)
    - Writings by others, 1943 (Box-folder 17: 12-15)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 17: 16)
  - 1950-1977
    - General (Box-folder 18: 1)
    - Bulletins (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Box-folder 18: 3)
      - 1956 (Box-folder 18: 4)
      - 1958-1960 (Box-folder 18: 5-7)
      - 1964 (Box-folder 18: 8)
      - 1965-1970 (Box-folder 18: 9-14)
      - 1971-1974 (Box-folder 19: 1-4)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 19: 5)
    - Memoranda
      - 1959 (Box-folder 19: 6)
      - 1964 (Box-folder 19: 7)
      - 1972 (Box-folder 19: 8)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 19: 9)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1977 (Box-folder 19: 10)
    - Newsletters (Box-folder 19: 11)
    - Notes (Box-folder 19: 12)
    - Organizational charts (Box-folder 19: 13)
    - Pamphlets (Box-folder 19: 14)
    - Press releases (Box-folder 19: 15)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 19: 16-19)
    - Remarks
      - Undated (Box-folder 20: 1)
      - 1960 (Box-folder 20: 2)
      - 1968 (Box-folder 20: 3)
      - 1970 (Box-folder 20: 4)
      - 1972-1974 (Box-folder 20: 5-7)
    - Reports
      - 1964 (Box-folder 20: 8)
      - 1973 (Box-folder 20: 9)
    - Statements
      - Undated (Box-folder 20: 10)
      - 1973 (Box-folder 20: 11)
    - Telegrams (Box-folder 20: 12)
    - Writings by others, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 20: 13)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 20: 14)
- Suez Canal Clearance File, 1952-1974 (Boxes 20-27)
  Articles, bulletins, charts and drawings, clippings, contracts, correspondence, cost of cleaning, diary, equipment used, plan, memoranda, minutes of meetings, newsletters, notes, personnel records, printed matter, remarks, reports, schedule, statements, telecommunication system and telegrams relating to the Suez Canal clearance operations under the direction of Raymond Wheeler at the request of the Secretary-General of the United Nations, arranged alphabetically by physical form. Includes materials in French and Arabic. See also: World Bank File.
  - General (Box-folder 20: 15)
  - Articles (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Bulletins (Box-folder 20: 17)
  - Charts and drawings (Box-folder 20: 18-20)
  - Charts and drawings (Box-folder 21: 1-2)
  - Chronological excerpts from salvage sitreps on ships (Box-folder 21: 3-4)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 21: 5-6)
  - Contracts (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Correspondence
    - Undated (Box-folder 21: 8)
    - 1952 January-February (Box-folder 21: 9)
    - 1956
      - January (Box-folder 21: 10)
      - October-December (Box-folder 21: 11)
    - 1957
      - January-March (Box-folder 21: 12-14)
      - April-July (Box-folder 22: 1-4)
      - September-October (Box-folder 22: 5-6)
      - December (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - 1958
      - January (Box-folder 22: 8)
      - April-June (Box-folder 22: 9-10)
      - August-September (Box-folder 22: 11)
      - November-December (Box-folder 22: 12)
    - 1959 September-December (Box-folder 22: 13)
    - 1960
      - January-March (Box-folder 22: 14)
      - August (Box-folder 22: 15)
      - October (Box-folder 22: 16)
    - 1964
      - May (Box-folder 22: 17)
      - December (Box-folder 22: 18)
    - 1965
      - February-March (Box-folder 22: 19)
      - August (Box-folder 22: 20)
    - 1966
      - February (Box-folder 22: 21)
      - April-June (Box-folder 22: 22)
    - 1967
      - March (Box-folder 22: 23)
      - June (Box-folder 22: 24)
      - December (Box-folder 22: 25)
    - 1968
      - February (Box-folder 22: 26)
      - April-May (Box-folder 22: 27)
      - September (Box-folder 22: 28)
    - 1970 December (Box-folder 22: 29)
    - 1971
      - January (Box-folder 22: 30)
      - March-April (Box-folder 22: 31)
      - May (Box-folder 22: 32)
      - June-July (Box-folder 22: 33)
      - August-September (Box-folder 22: 34)
      - October-December (Box-folder 22: 35)
    - 1972 May (Box-folder 22: 36)
    - 1973
      - May-June (Box-folder 22: 37)
      - October (Box-folder 22: 38)
      - November-December (Box-folder 22: 39)
    - 1974 January (Box-folder 22: 40)
  - Cost assessment (Box-folder 22: 41)
  - Diary (Box-folder 22: 42)
  - List of equipments (Box-folder 22: 43)
  - Maps (Box-folder 22: 44)
  - Memoranda
    - Undated (Box-folder 22: 45)
    - 1956 November (Box-folder 22: 46)
    - 1957
      - January-February (Box-folder 22: 47)
      - April (Box-folder 22: 48)
      - June (Box-folder 22: 49)
      - September (Box-folder 22: 50)
      - December (Box-folder 22: 51)
    - 1958
      - January-February (Box-folder 23: 1)
      - April-May (Box-folder 23: 2)
      - July (Box-folder 23: 3)
    - 1971 May (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Minutes of meetings
    - Undated (Box-folder 23: 5)
    - 1956
      - June (Box-folder 23: 6)
      - October-November (Box-folder 23: 7-8)
    - 1957 December (Box-folder 23: 9)
    - 1958 April (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - News releases
    - Undated (Box-folder 23: 11)
    - 1957 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Notes
    - Undated (Box-folder 23: 13-14)
    - 1957 (Box-folder 23: 15)
    - 1958 (Box-folder 23: 16)
    - 1965-1966 (Box-folder 23: 17)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 23: 18)
  - Personnel records (Box-folder 23: 19)
  - Plans of operations (Box-folder 23: 20)
  - Policy statements (Box-folder 23: 21)
  - Press releases
    - Undated (Box-folder 23: 22)
    - 1958 (Box-folder 23: 23)
    - 1959 (Box-folder 23: 24)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 23: 25-27)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Remarks
    - Undated (Box-folder 24: 2)
    - 1957 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Reports
    - Undated (Box-folder 24: 4)
    - 1955 (Box-folder 24: 5)
    - 1956 (Box-folder 24: 6-7)
    - 1956-1957 (Box-folder 24: 8)
    - 1957 (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - 1959 (Box-folder 25: 2)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 25: 3)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 25: 4-5)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 25: 6-7)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - 1973? (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Rules of navigation and tide tables (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Schedule (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Statements (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Suez Canal requirements and capacity (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Tanks and vessels (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Telecommunications system (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Telegrams
    - Incoming
      - Undated (Box-folder 26: 9)
      - 1956 (Box-folder 26: 10)
      - 1957 January-May (Box-folder 26: 11-12)
      - 1958 (Box-folder 26: 13)
      - 1959 (Box-folder 26: 14)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 26: 15)
    - Outgoing
      - Undated (Box-folder 26: 16)
      - 1956 January (Box-folder 26: 17)
      - 1957 January-April (Box-folder 27: 1-4)
      - 1959 April (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Wrecks removal log (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 27: 7)
- Mekong River Basin File, 1957-1974 (Boxes 27-33)
  Clippings, communique, correspondence, cost of the project, data used, description of the project, drawings and tables, financial plan, funding agreement, list of participants and itinerary, legal documents, maps, memoranda, minutes of meetings, messages, newsletters, notes, press releases, printed matter, reports, schedule of work, speech, statements, and telegrams relating to the multi-purpose development of the Lower Mekong River Basin, encompassing portions of Thailand, Laos, Cambodia, and Vietnam, under the leadership of Raymond Wheeler as head of the United Nations mission and the terms of reference, arranged alphabetically by physical form. Also includes correspondence, memoranda, and writings by Virginia Wheeler in her official capacity as a legal adviser to the United Nations in the Mekong River Basin project. Includes materials in French and Vietnamese. See also: United Nations File.
  - General (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Communique (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Committee for the Co-Ordination of Investigations of the Lower Mekong Basin file (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Correspondence
    - Undated (Box-folder 27: 12)
    - 1957 June-December (Box-folder 27: 13-14)
    - 1958
      - January (Box-folder 27: 15)
      - March (Box-folder 27: 16)
      - July (Box-folder 27: 17)
    - 1960 March (Box-folder 27: 18)
    - 1962 November-December (Box-folder 27: 19)
    - 1963
      - January (Box-folder 27: 20)
      - May (Box-folder 27: 21)
      - July-September (Box-folder 27: 22)
      - November-December (Box-folder 27: 23)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 27: 24-28)
    - 1965 February-December (Box-folder 27: 29-33)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 28: 1-6)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 28: 7-14)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 28: 15-26)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 28: 27-35)
    - 1970
      - January-May (Box-folder 29: 1)
      - July (Box-folder 29: 2)
      - September-November (Box-folder 29: 3)
    - 1971
      - January-June (Box-folder 29: 4-5)
      - August-September (Box-folder 29: 6)
      - November-December (Box-folder 29: 7)
    - 1972
      - February (Box-folder 29: 8)
      - May (Box-folder 29: 9)
      - July-December (Box-folder 29: 10-11)
    - 1973
      - August (Box-folder 29: 12)
      - October (Box-folder 29: 13)
      - November-December (Box-folder 29: 14)
    - 1974
      - January-February (Box-folder 29: 15)
      - June (Box-folder 29: 16)
  - Cost assessment (Box-folder 29: 17)
  - Data on Mekong development (Box-folder 29: 18)
  - Description of project and terms of reference (Box-folder 29: 19)
  - Drawings and tables (Box-folder 29: 20)
  - Expense vouchers (Box-folder 29: 21)
  - Financial plan (Box-folder 29: 22)
  - Funding agreement (Box-folder 29: 23)
  - Itinerary and forwarding addresses (Box-folder 29: 24)
  - Legal documents (Box-folder 29: 25)
  - Legislative texts and documentation (Box-folder 29: 26)
  - List of participants (Box-folder 29: 27)
  - Maps (Box-folder 29: 28)
  - Memoranda
    - Undated (Box-folder 29: 29)
    - 1961 December (Box-folder 29: 30)
    - 1964
      - January-August (Box-folder 29: 31-32)
      - October-December (Box-folder 29: 33)
    - 1965
      - January-August (Box-folder 29: 34-36)
      - December (Box-folder 29: 37)
    - 1966
      - January (Box-folder 29: 38)
      - April (Box-folder 29: 39)
      - July-October (Box-folder 29: 40-41)
      - December (Box-folder 29: 42)
    - 1967
      - February-May (Box-folder 30: 1-2)
      - August-November (Box-folder 30: 3-4)
    - 1968
      - January-July (Box-folder 30: 5-6)
      - September (Box-folder 30: 7)
      - November-December (Box-folder 30: 8)
    - 1969
      - January (Box-folder 30: 9)
      - April-December (Box-folder 30: 10-13)
    - 1970
      - January-February (Box-folder 30: 14)
      - May (Box-folder 30: 15)
    - 1971
      - February (Box-folder 30: 16)
      - April (Box-folder 30: 17)
      - October-December (Box-folder 30: 18)
    - 1972
      - April (Box-folder 30: 19)
      - August (Box-folder 30: 20)
    - 1973 October-November (Box-folder 30: 21)
  - Messages (Box-folder 30: 22)
  - Minutes of meetings
    - General (Box-folder 30: 23)
    - 1958 January (Box-folder 30: 24)
    - 1963 November (Box-folder 30: 25)
    - 1964 April (Box-folder 30: 26)
    - 1965 January (Box-folder 30: 27)
    - 1966 January (Box-folder 30: 28)
    - 1967 April (Box-folder 30: 29)
    - 1968
      - May (Box-folder 30: 30)
      - December (Box-folder 30: 31)
    - 1969
      - January-February (Box-folder 30: 32)
      - April-July (Box-folder 30: 33-34)
      - November (Box-folder 30: 35)
    - 1970 November-December (Box-folder 30: 36)
    - 1971
      - April-June (Box-folder 30: 37)
      - August (Box-folder 30: 38)
    - 1972
      - June (Box-folder 30: 39)
      - August (Box-folder 30: 40)
    - 1973 November-December (Box-folder 30: 41)
  - Newsletters
    - Undated (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - 1957-1958 (Box-folder 31: 2-3)